Associated Students of Duke University Records, 1965 - 1991 UA.31.02.0003
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Associated Students of Duke University records
1965-1991
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Associated Students of Duke University
UA.31.02.0003
40 Linear Feet 80 boxes
The Associated Students of Duke University (ASDU) was the student government at Duke from 1967 to 1993. It originated in March 1967 when the student body voted to merge the Men's Student Government Association and the Women's Student Government Association. ASDU consisted of an executive branch and a legislative branch. A student referendum in April 1993 replaced ASDU with a new organization, Duke Student Government, in which the legislative and executive branches were consolidated. ASDU records consist of minutes, correspondence, legislation, reports, printed matter, judicial decisions, charters, memoranda, speeches, receipts, vouchers, and other records. The ASDU records provide insight into student life during a time when students were becoming more active in university affairs. The records also document student organizations at Duke at this time and demonstrate some of the services provided to students by ASDU.
Access Restrictions
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
Records of the University's Board of Trustees which have been existence for at least fifty years are available for scholarly research with the permission of the University Archivist. Access to records which have been in existence for less than fifty years shall be granted only by special permission, in writing, from the Board of Trustees.
In accordance with the Family Education Rights and Privacy Act of 1974 as amended, Duke University permits students to inspect their education records and limits the disclosure of personally identifiable information from education records.
Provenance
The Associated Students of Duke University Records was received by the University Archives as a transfer in 1971-2004.
Historical Note
The Associated Students of Duke University (ASDU), the student government from 1967-1993, originated in March 1967, when the student body voted to merge the Men's Student Government Association and the Women's Student Government Association. ASDU began its duties in the Fall of 1967 with Jon Kinney serving as the first President.
ASDU was divided into Executive and Legislative branches. The Executive was made up of the President, Vice President(s), other officers, and the Executive cabinet. Officers were elected to one-year terms. The President had veto power over legislation passed by the Legislature. The Legislature consisted of representatives elected by members of individual schools and colleges and met weekly. The Legislature was responsible for enacting legislation pertaining to student welfare, chartering all student organizations, and approving Presidential appointments. A President's veto could be overturned by a two-thirds majority vote. A Speaker was elected to preside over the Legislature.
A student referendum passed in April 1993 replaced ASDU with a new student government which featured the consolidation of the legislative and executive branches. The new organization was called the Duke Student Government (DSG).
Collection Overview
The records of the Associated Students of Duke University span from 1965-1991, covering the years that ASDU existed, as well as a few items prior to the establishment of ASDU in 1967. The bulk of the material focuses on the 1970s and early 1980s. The records consist of agendas and minutes, charters, correspondence and memoranda, resolutions and statutes, reports, studies, financial material, photographs, newspaper clippings and other printed matter.
The ASDU records provide insight into student life during a time when students were becoming more active in university affairs. The collection is useful in examining issues that were important to students in the 1970s and 1980s such as divestment in South Africa, financial aid and campus race relations and the actions taken on those issues; how effective student government was during this period; and also illuminates student organizations at Duke at this time -- both what they were and what they did. The records also demonstrate some of the services provided to students by ASDU: the Bail Loan Fund; Legal assistance; van/shuttle services; and the distribution of the Student Activities fee.
Additional ASDU records can be found inter-filed with Duke Student Government records. Please contact University Archives for additional information.
Related Material
Duke Student Government Records, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Men's Student Government Association Records, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Woman's Student Government Association Records, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Student participation in administration; Disinvestment; Student activities -- North Carolina; Duke University -- Student housing; Student government; Duke University. Student Government; Duke University -- Students -- Societies, etc.; Duke University -- Students; Associated Students of Duke University; Griffith, William; Duke University. Reggie Howard Memorial Scholarship Fund; Moyle, Shep
- Student Organizations, 1963-1990; 1
  - Accounting+ M.S. Majors Unions (Box 8)
  - Afghanistan Action Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 8)
  - Aid to American Indians at Duke, 1977 (Box 8)
  - A.I.E.S.EC. (International Association of Students in Economics and Commerce), 1984 (Box 8)
  - Air Force Club, undated (Box 8)
  - Alliance Against Racism and Political Oppression, 1976 (Box 8)
  - Alpha Cube, 1983 (Box 8)
  - Alpha Phi Omega Service Organization, undated (Box 8)
  - Alternative Productions, 1981 (Box 8)
  - Alspaugh, 1988 (Box 8)
  - A.Y.D. (Alternatives for Youth in Durham), 1983 (Box 8)
  - Amateur Radio Association, 1973-1981 (Box 9)
  - American Field Service, 1978-1980 (Box 9)
  - A.S.C.E. (American Society of Civil Engineers), 1976-1984 (Box 9)
  - A.S.M.E. (American Society of Mechanical Engineers), 1983-1984 (Box 9)
  - A.S.P.A. (American Society for Personnel Administration), 1983-1984 (Box 9)
  - American Student Federation, 1979 (Box 9)
  - Anti-Klan Coalition, 1980 (Box 9)
  - Another Drama Group, 1978 (Box 9)
  - Anthropology Majors Union, 1983 (Box 9)
  - Association of African Students, undated (Box 9)
  - Association of Women's Residences, undated (Box 9)
  - Archery Club, 1976 (Box 9)
  - Arms Control Study Group, 1983 (Box 9)
  - Arnold Air Society/Angel Flight, 1982-1984 (Box 9)
  - Art Majors Union, undated (Box 9)
  - Asian Students Association, 1982-1988 (Box 9)
  - A.C.M. (Association for Computing Majors), 1983-1985 (Box 9)
  - The Archive, 1988 (Box 9)
  - (A.I.A.W.)Duke Association of Intercollegiate Athletics for Women, undated (Box 9)
  - Astrology Club, undated (Box 9)
  - Astronomy Club, undated (Box 9)
  - Aycock House, undated (Box 9)
  - Bahai Club, 1975-1977 (Box 9)
  - Badminton Team, undated (Box 9)
  - Bassett Project, undated (Box 9)
  - Bellydance Association, 1976 (Box 9)
  - Bench and Bar Society, undated (Box 9)
  - Billiards Club, 1978-1979 (Box 9)
  - Biomedical Engineering Society, 1982-1985 (Box 10)
  - Bioscience Majors Union, 1981-1984 (Box 10)
  - Black Student Alliance, 1984-1988 (Box 10)
  - Black Yearbook (Ebony Visions), 1978-1979 (Box 10)
  - Bread for the World, 1983 (Box 10)
  - Bridge Club, undated (Box 10)
  - Buchanan Living Group, undated (Box 10)
  - Buisness Club, 1976 (Box 10)
  - C.C.C (Campus Community Council), undated (Box 10)
  - Campus Crusade for Christ, undated (Box 10)
  - Campus Ministries, 1986-1987 (Box 10)
  - Career Network, undated (Box 10)
  - Central American Solidarity Committee, 1983 (Box 10)
  - CHANCE, 1988-1989 (Box 10)
  - Center for Tension Control, 1976-1983 (Box 10)
  - The Chanticleer, 1988 (Box 10)
  - Chess Club, 1983-1985 (Box 10)
  - Chinese Club (Zao Fan Ju Le Bu), 1986-1987 (Box 10)
  - Christian Science Organization, 1986-1987 (Box 10)
  - Duke Christian Fellowship, undated (Box 10)
  - The Chronicle, 1979-1985 (Box 10)
  - The Chronicle, 1 of 2, 1985-1989 (Box 10)
  - The Chronicle, 2 of 2, 1985-1989 (Box 10)
  - Circle K International, 1985 (Box 10)
  - Chinese Student Association, 1982 (Box 10)
  - CIRCUNA (Council on International Relations+ United Nations Affairs), undated (Box 10)
  - Coalition for Alternatives to Shearon Harris, 1986 (Box 10)
  - Coffeehouse, 1981-1984 (Box 11)
  - Collegiate Bowl, 1979-1984 (Box 11)
  - Colorblind?, 1986-1987 (Box 11)
  - Committee of Experiential Education, undated (Box 11)
  - Committee for Racial Understanding, undated (Box 11)
  - Committee for the Sirena Wu Dunn Memorial Scholarship, 1985-1986 (Box 11)
  - Community Environmental Education Thru Duke, 1977 (Box 11)
  - Community on the Middle East Peace Process, 1980 (Box 11)
  - Comparative Area Studies Majors Union, 1984-1989 (Box 11)
  - Duke Companions, 1984 (Box 11)
  - Contemporary Fiction Group, 1976 (Box 11)
  - Council for Exceptional Children, undated (Box 11)
  - Crew, 1975-1981 (Box 11)
  - Cricket Club, undated (Box 11)
  - Cycling League (Box 11)
  - Cyclists League, 1977-1981 (Box 11)
  - Dance Group, undated (Box 11)
  - Dating Service, 1985 (Box 11)
  - De Toqueville Society (Box 11)
  - Debate Team, 1973-1982 (Box 11)
  - Delta Phi Alpha Honor Society, 1984-1985 (Box 11)
  - Duke Democrats, 1982-1985 (Box 11)
  - Duke Energy Action Committee, 1984 (Box 11)
  - The Duke Engineer, undated (Box 11)
  - Duke Players, undated (Box 11)
  - The Duke Pre-Medical Society, undated (Box 11)
  - Duke Students for a Democratic Society, undated (Box 11)
  - Duke Students Economic Association, 1981 (Box 11)
  - Duke Students Humanities Reivew, 1982 (Box 11)
  - D.I.P.E.C. (Duke Israel Politics + Eduction Review), 1982-1984 (Box 11)
  - Duke for Dukakis, 1988 (Box 11)
  - Duke Students for George Bush, 1988 (Box 11)
  - Duke Students for John Anderson, 1988 (Box 11)
  - Duke Students for Ron Paul, 1988 (Box 11)
  - Duke Students for Terry Sanford, undated (Box 11)
  - DRAGO (Duke Recreational Gaming Organization), 1983-1984 (Box 11)
  - DSAEE, undated (Box 11)
  - DUDA (Duke University Discordian Alliance), 1986-1987 (Box 11)
  - DUMB (Duke University Marching Band), 1984-1987 (Box 11)
  - Duke Young Voters for the President, undated (Box 11)
  - Durham Community Learning Exchange, undated (Box 11)
  - Durham ECOS, undated (Box 11)
  - Durham International Folk Dance Club, undated (Box 12)
  - ECOS, 1981-1984 (Box 12)
  - Education Majors Union, 1978-1980 (Box 12)
  - El Circulo Hispano, undated (Box 12)
  - Engineering Promotion Council, 1983 (Box 12)
  - Engineering Student Government, undated (Box 12)
  - The Environmental Symposium, undated (Box 12)
  - Epworth Dormitory (Box 12)
  - Equestrian Club, 1976-1982 (Box 12)
  - Eta Kappa Nu, 1986-1987 (Box 12)
  - Duke Experimental Living/Learning, 1986 (Box 12)
  - FASST, 1986 (Box 12)
  - Fencing Club, 1978-1980 (Box 12)
  - Few Federation Seminars, 1979 (Box 12)
  - Female Affiliates of Duke Soccer, 1981 (Box 12)
  - Field Hockey, undated (Box 12)
  - Duke First Ranger Company, 1981 (Box 12)
  - Duke Folk Ensemble, 1976 (Box 12)
  - Football Club, 1981-1981 (Box 12)
  - Duke Freeman, 1985-1986 (Box 12)
  - Free Speech Club, undated (Box 12)
  - Friendship Association of Chinese Students and Scholars, 1984 (Box 12)
  - Friendship Festival, 1984 (Box 12)
  - Frisbee Club, 1978-1981 (Box 12)
  - Flying Club, undated (Box 12)
  - Freshman Advisory Council, 1988-1989 (Box 12)
  - Gay Alliance, 1972-1989 (Box 12)
  - Geology Majors Union, 1981-1986 (Box 12)
  - German Club, undated (Box 12)
  - Graduate Student Association, undated (Box 12)
  - Duke Campus Girl Scouts, 1979-1982 (Box 12)
  - Gymnastics Club, 1979-1980 (Box 12)
  - Handbell Choir, 1986-1987 (Box 12)
  - Health Sciences Association, 1983 (Box 12)
  - Hillel, 1982-1984 (Box 12)
  - History Majors Union, 1980-1984 (Box 12)
  - Homecoming Issue, 1980 (Box 12)
  - Hoof'n'Horn, 1973 (Box 13)
  - House H, undated (Box 13)
  - House I, undated (Box 13)
  - Hunger Teach-In, 1988 (Box 13)
  - I.E.E.E. (Institute of Electrical and Electronic Engineers), 1982-1984 (Box 13)
  - Ice Hockey Club, 1975-1981 (Box 13)
  - Duke India Assocation, 1984-1989 (Box 13)
  - Interfraternity Council (IFC), undated (Box 13)
  - International Club, undated (Box 13)
  - I.L.A.P International League for Animal Protection, undated (Box 13)
  - International Relations Association, undated (Box 13)
  - Inter-Varsity Christian Fellowship, undated (Box 13)
  - Interview Magazine, 1983-1984 (Box 13)
  - Investment Club, 1984 (Box 13)
  - Duke Jazz Ensemble, undated (Box 13)
  - Duke Jazz Society, 1984-1987 (Box 13)
  - Joe Baldwin Committee (Box 13)
  - Karamu, 1987 (Box 13)
  - Karate-do Club, undated (Box 13)
  - Kung-fu Club, undated (Box 13)
  - Kayak Club, undated (Box 13)
  - Kyokushinikan Karate Club, 1976 (Box 13)
  - Lacrosse (womens), 1977-1981 (Box 13)
  - Lancaster Language Dorm, 1988 (Box 13)
  - Latter-Day Saints Students Association, undated (Box 13)
  - Duke Libertarians, 1983-1985 (Box 13)
  - Mini-Baha Club, 1983 (Box 13)
  - Duke Mediation Organization, undated (Box 13)
  - Men's Alliance, undated (Box 13)
  - Duke Model United Nations Group, undated (Box 13)
  - Movement for Progress and Development, 1985 (Box 13)
  - Duke Music Association, 1981-1983 (Box 13)
  - Neridians, 1979-1982 (Box 13)
  - New American Movement (NAM), undated (Box 13)
  - The Newman Community, undated (Box 13)
  - North Carolina Action for Farmworkers, undated (Box 13)
  - North Carolina Public Interest Research Group, undated (Box 13)
  - North Carolina Student Legislature, 1987 (Box 13)
  - North Carolina Student Rural Health Coalition, 1981-1986 (Box 13)
  - Objectivist Club, 1987 (Box 13)
  - Operation Love, 1979 (Box 14)
  - Orchid Society, 1977 (Box 14)
  - Outing Club, 1984 (Box 14)
  - D.O.L.C.E., 1979 (Box 14)
  - Orthodox Student Association, 1978 (Box 14)
  - Panhellenic Council, 1982 (Box 14)
  - Parcheesi Society, 1978 (Box 14)
  - Duke Partners, 1983-1984 (Box 14)
  - Peacemaking in a Nuclear Age, 1984 (Box 14)
  - People's Intergalatic Food Conspiracy Inc, 1973-1975 (Box 14)
  - People's Peace Treaty, 1971 (Box 14)
  - Phi Gamma Tau fraternity, undated (Box 14)
  - Pep Board, 1963 (Box 14)
  - Duke Photo Group, 1983 (Box 14)
  - Photographic Society, 1976-1982 (Box 14)
  - P.I.S.C.E.S., 1979-1983 (Box 14)
  - Phi Sigma Alpha, 1986 (Box 14)
  - People Productions, 1977 (Box 14)
  - Philosophy Club, 1979-1981 (Box 14)
  - Duke Pitchforks, 1981 (Box 14)
  - Political Science Majors Union, 1977-1984 (Box 14)
  - Pyscology Majors Club, 1982 (Box 14)
  - Polo Club, 1986 (Box 14)
  - Progressive Political Union, 1982 (Box 14)
  - Project for Understandingn of the Rural South, 1984 (Box 14)
  - Project WILD, 1981 (Box 14)
  - Public Lands Policy Study Group, 1984 (Box 14)
  - Public Policy Majors Union, 1981-1984 (Box 14)
  - Publications Board, 1 of 3, 1984-1989 (Box 14)
  - Publications Board, 2 of 3, 1984-1989 (Box 15)
  - Publications Board, 3 of 3, 1984-1989 (Box 15)
  - Publications Board: Computer, 1986 (Box 15)
  - Radio Board, 1987-1988 (Box 15)
  - Radical Academic Union, 1976-1977 (Box 15)
  - Reading Center Club (Box 15)
  - Reginald R. Howard Memorial Organization, 1984 (Box 15)
  - College Republicans, 1977-1983 (Box 15)
  - Rugby Club, 1977-1982 (Box 15)
  - Russian Club, 1983-1987 (Box 15)
  - Sailing Club, 1970-1981 (Box 15)
  - Save the Efe Pygmies, 1982-1983 (Box 15)
  - Science Club, 1987 (Box 15)
  - SARC, 1989 (Box 15)
  - Scuba Club, 1980-1981 (Box 15)
  - Signs of Silence, 1983 (Box 15)
  - Ski Team, undated (Box 15)
  - Skeet Club, undated (Box 15)
  - Ski Devils, 1979-1981 (Box 15)
  - Skydevils Parachute Club, 1979-1981 (Box 15)
  - Student Migrant Action Coalition, 1978 (Box 16)
  - Soccer Club, 1974-1981 (Box 16)
  - Social Dance Club, 1986 (Box 16)
  - Society for Black Engineers, 1979-1983 (Box 16)
  - Society on Culture, Illness and Healing, 1983 (Box 16)
  - Society for Creative Anchronism, 1981-1982 (Box 16)
  - Society of Physics Students, 1981 (Box 16)
  - Society for Religious Understanding, 1983 (Box 16)
  - Society of Women Engineers, 1981-1982 (Box 16)
  - Sociology Majors Union, 1976-1981 (Box 16)
  - Wome's Softball, 1980-1981 (Box 16)
  - South Africa Coalition, 1984 (Box 16)
  - Soviet Jewry Task Force, 1978 (Box 16)
  - S.A.L.S.A (Spanish American Latino Students Association), 1983-1989 (Box 16)
  - Sports Club Council, 1 of 3, 1978-1986 (Box 16)
  - Sports Club Council, 2 of 3, 1978-1986 (Box 16)
  - Sports Club Council, 3 of 3, 1978-1986 (Box 16)
  - Sports Clubs, 1989-1990 (Box 16)
  - Sports Club Council: Reference File, 1974-1981 (Box 16)
  - Sports Car Club, undated (Box 17)
  - Squash Club, 1978 (Box 17)
  - Student/Faculty Cooperative Movement, 1978 (Box 17)
  - Stonehenge Musical Society, undated (Box 17)
  - Students Against World Hunger, 1981 (Box 17)
  - Student Activist Week, 1989 (Box 17)
  - The Student's Association of Russia, undated (Box 17)
  - Students for a Democratic Central America, 1984 (Box 17)
  - Students for Energy Awareness, 1982 (Box 17)
  - Students for the Exploration of Development of Space, 1981-1984 (Box 17)
  - Students for Gore, 1987 (Box 17)
  - Duke Students for Life, 1981-1984 (Box 17)
  - Duke Students for a Middle East Understanding, 1983 (Box 17)
  - Students for Simon, 1987 (Box 17)
  - Student Health Career Association, 1980 (Box 17)
  - Student National Medical Association, 1984-1987 (Box 17)
  - Duke Student Nurse's Association, 1978-1981 (Box 17)
  - STEPS (Students Towards Equality and Prevention of Sexism), 1978 (Box 17)
  - Duke Student Tutors, 1982-1984 (Box 17)
  - Subbuteo Club, 1987 (Box 17)
  - Sufists Club, 1986 (Box 17)
  - Summer Appalachian Project, 1979 (Box 17)
  - Symposium Committee, 1981-1988 (Box 17)
  - Table Tennis Club, undated (Box 17)
  - Tennis Club, 1976-1981 (Box 17)
  - Theologian in Residence Committee, 1980 (Box 17)
  - Track Club, 1980-1981 (Box 17)
  - Television Club, undated (Box 17)
  - Transfer Committee, 1981 (Box 17)
  - Twirling Ensemble, undated (Box 17)
  - Duke University Union, 1 of 4, 1976-1989 (Box 17)
  - Duke University Union, 2 of 4, 1976-1989 (Box 17)
  - Duke University Union, 3 of 4, 1976-1989 (Box 18)
  - Duke University Union, 4 of 4, 1976-1989 (Box 18)
  - United Duke Students, 1981 (Box 18)
  - United Jewish Appeal, undated (Box 18)
  - Unitef Students of America, 1983 (Box 18)
  - Volunteers for Youth, 1980-1984 (Box 18)
  - Duke University Volunteer Services, 1986 (Box 18)
  - Volleyball Club, 1979-1982 (Box 18)
  - Water Polo Club, 1978-1981 (Box 18)
  - Wargamers Club, 1980-1982 (Box 18)
  - The Way Biblical Research and Teaching Fellowship, undated (Box 18)
  - WDUK, undated (Box 18)
  - WDBS, undated (Box 18)
  - WXDU, 1984-1989 (Box 18)
  - Wind Symphony, 1972-1989 (Box 18)
  - Winners Circle, 1977 (Box 18)
  - Women's Interest League, 1984 (Box 18)
  - Women's Alliance, undated (Box 18)
  - Women's Coalition, undated (Box 18)
  - Worker-Student Alliance, 1975 (Box 19)
  - Yoga Club, undated (Box 19)
  - York House, undated (Box 19)
  - Young Conservatives, 1983 (Box 19)
  - Youth Outreach Steering Committee, 1983 (Box 19)
  - YMCA/YWCA, 1970-1980 (Box 19)
  - Duke Youth Caucus, 1980 (Box 19)
  - Duke Youth Companionship, undated (Box 19)
  - Duke Youth Outreach, 1981 (Box 19)
  - Zionist Action Coalition, 1980 (Box 19)
  - Zoology Majors Union, 1978 (Box 19)
  - Charters, 1969-1970 (Box 19)
  - Charters, 1970-1971 (Box 19)
  - Charters, 1971-1972 (Box 19)
  - Charters, 1972-1973 (Box 19)
  - Charters, 1973-1974 (Box 19)
  - Charters, 1974-1975 (Box 19)
  - Charters, 1975-1976 (Box 19)
  - Charters, 1976-1977 (Box 19)
  - Charters, 1977-1978 (Box 19)
  - Charters, 1978-1979 (Box 19)
  - Charters, 1979-1980 (Box 19)
  - Charters, 1980-1981 (Box 19)
  - Charters, 1982-1983 (Box 20)
  - Late Charters, 1982-1983 (Box 20)
  - Charters, 1984-1985 (Box 20)
  - Groups Chartered, 1984-1985 (Box 20)
  - Charter Requests, 1985 (Box 20)
  - Official Recognition, 1985-1986 (Box 20)
  - Charters (Approved Charter Requests), 1985-1986 (Box 20)
  - Charters (Approved Charter Requests), 1986-1987 (Box 20)
  - Charters, 1987-1988 (Box 20)
  - Charters, 1988-1989 (Box 20)
  - Chartering Review, 1985 (Box 20)
  - SoC Evaluation Committee, 1 of 2, 1985 (Box 20)
  - SoC Evaluation Committee, 2 of 2, 1985 (Box 20)
  - Directories, 1970-1980 (Box 20)
  - Bookeeping Course, undated (Box 21)
  - Current Forms, undated (Box 21)
  - Chartering and Budgeting Procedures, 1982 (Box 21)
  - Political Organizations Chartering Rules, 1982 (Box 21)
  - Speakers Policies, 1982 (Box 21)
  - Student Organizations Committee, 1968-1988 (Box 21)
  - Miscellaneous, 1982; 2 folders (Box 21)
- Financial Materials, 1968-1990; 2
  Scope and Contents
  The Financial Materials subseries contain the records of the ASDU Treasurer and Business Manager. The series features budgetary materials for the ASDU general administration and budget requests and audits for ASDU funded student organizations. The Financial materials series also includes information about the funding of ASDU student services such as an ASDU sponsored lawyer.
  - Financial Material, 1968-1972 (Box 21)
  - Financial Material, 1968 (Box 21)
  - Financial Material (Includes Student Activities Fees), 1969 (Box 21)
  - Budget, 1970 (Box 21)
  - Statements, 1970-1971 (Box 22)
  - Bills, 1970 (Box 22)
  - Treasurer's Statements, 1970 (Box 22)
  - ASDU General Journal, 1970-1972 (Box 22)
  - Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box 22)
  - Account Book, 1971 (Box 22)
  - Accounts (checking+savings), 1971-1973 (Box 22)
  - Audit Corrections, 1971 (Box 22)
  - Budget, 1971 (Box 22)
  - Correspondence, 1971 (Box 22)
  - Student Activities Fee, 1972 (Box 22)
  - Financial Material, 1972 (Box 22)
  - Student Organizations, A-Duke G, 1972 (Box 22)
  - Student Organizations, Duke J-M, 1973 (Box 22)
  - Student Organizations, N-Y, 1972 (Box 23)
  - Financial Statements, 1973 (Box 23)
  - Student Organizations, 1973 (Box 23)
  - Budget, 1973 (Box 23)
  - Budget Questionnaire (other institutions), 1973 (Box 23)
  - Budget Commission, 1974-1976 (Box 23)
  - Financial Material, 1975-1977 (Box 23)
  - Budget Commission, 1975-1976 (Box 23)
  - Budget Commission 1 of 2, 1975-1977 (Box 23)
  - Budget Commission 2 of 2, 1975-1977 (Box 23)
  - Student Organizations-Allocations, 1976-1977 (Box 23)
  - Student Organizations, 1976-1977 (Box 24)
  - Student Organizations-Audits, 1976-1977 (Box 24)
  - Executive Budgets, 1969-1976 (Box 24)
  - Budget Commission, 1976-1979 (Box 24)
  - ASDU Budget Requets, 1977-1979 (Box 24)
  - Miscellaneous, 1977 (Box 24)
  - Budgets, 1978-1979 (Box 24)
  - Budgets (ASDU Student Organizations) (Box 25)
  - Student Organizations--Audits, 1977-1978 (Box 25)
  - Student Organizations, 1978-1979 (Box 25)
  - Student Organizations-Budget Recommendations, 1978-1979 (Box 25)
  - Student Organizations--Audits, 1978-1979 (Box 25)
  - Audits, 1978-1979 (Box 25)
  - ASDU Legal Services, 1978-1979 (Box 25)
  - Student Organizations-Financial Income Statements, 1979-1980 (Box 25)
  - Student Organizations--Budget Requets, 1979-1980 (Box 25)
  - Student Organizations--Audits, 1979-1980 (Box 25)
  - Heard and Approved Budgets, 1979-1980 (Box 26)
  - ASDU Budget Files, 1 of 3, 1980 (Box 26)
  - ASDU Budget Files, 2 of 3, 1980 (Box 26)
  - ASDU Budget Files, 3 of 3, 1980 (Box 26)
  - Financial Materials, 1980-1981 (Box 26)
  - Student Organizations--Waivers, 1980-1981 (Box 26)
  - Student Organizations--Budgets, 1980-1981 (Box 26)